[
  {
    "front": "May the . . . be with you",
    "back": "force"
  },
  {
    "front": "Laugh it up . . .",
    "back": "fuzzball"
  },
  {
    "front": "“When . . . years old, you reach… Look as good, you will not.”",
    "back": "900"
  },
  {
    "front": "Join me, and together we can rule the . . . as father and son.”",
    "back": "galaxy"
  },
  {
    "front": "It's a . . .!",
    "back": "trap"
  },
  {
    "front": "Aren't you a little . . .for a storm trooper?",
    "back": "short"
  },
  {
    "front": "I find your lack of . . .disturbing.",
    "back": "faith"
  },
   {
    "front": "I suggest a new strategy, R2: let the . . . win.",
    "back": "Wookiee"
  },
    {
    "front": "One thing's for sure, we're all going to be a lot . . .  .",
    "back": "thinner"
  },
    {
    "front": "Sir, the possibility of successfully navigating an . . . is approximately 3,720 to 1.",
    "back": "asteroid field"
  },
    {
    "front": "You came in that thing? You're . . .than I thought",
    "back": "braver"
  },
    {
    "front": "Help me . . ., you're my only hope.",
    "back": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
  }
]